<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MY SAFETY</string>
    <string name="txt">Safety fits like a Glove ; Try One On</string>
    <string name="heading">Help is Just A Shake Away</string>
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>
    <string name="okay">TODO</string>
    <string name="new1">TODO</string>
    <string name="plz">i dont know /n</string>
    <string name="please">TODO</string>
    <string name="image">image</string>
    <string name="add_your_contacts">ADD YOUR CONTACTS</string>
    <string name="contact_number">Contact Number</string>
    <string name="cn2">Contact Number</string>
    <string name="contact_number3">Contact Number</string>
    <string name="contact_number4">Contact Number</string>
    <string name="submit">SUBMIT</string>
    <string name="contact_number5">Contact Number</string>
    <string name="video">video</string>
    <string name="sound">sound</string>
    <string name="button_3">Button 3</string>
    <string name="fab">TODO</string>
    <string name="fab2">TODO</string>
    <string name="fab3">TODO</string>
    <string name="fab4">TODO</string>
    <string name="fab6">TODO</string>
    <string name="fab5">TODO</string>
    <string name="google_maps_api_key">YOUR_GOOGLE_MAPS_API_KEY_HERE</string>
    <string name="spark_women">Spark Women</string>
    <string name="app_id">ca-app-pub-3940256099942544~3347511713</string>
    <string name="banner_id">ca-app-pub-3940256099942544/6300978111</string>
    <string name="laws"><b>LAWS FOR WOMEN AND SECURITY</b>
        <b>1. The Protection of Women from Domestic Violence Act, 2005 (PWDVA)</b>
This act provides protection to women from domestic violence, which includes physical, emotional, sexual, and economic abuse. It also provides remedies like protection orders, residence orders, and monetary relief.
It allows women to seek help from the police, magistrates, or protection officers to ensure their safety.<br />
        <b>2. Indian Penal Code (IPC) – Sections Related to Sexual Harassment and Assault</b>
Section 354: Protects women from acts that intend to outrage their modesty, such as assault or force.
Section 354A: Defines and penalizes sexual harassment, including unwelcome physical contact, demands for sexual favors, and sexually colored remarks.
Section 354C (Voyeurism): Penalizes capturing or sharing images of a woman engaging in a private act without her consent.
Section 376: Covers rape, providing stringent punishment for the crime, and includes provisions on consent.<br />
   <br /> <b>3. The Sexual Harassment of Women at Workplace (Prevention, Prohibition, and Redressal) Act, 2013</b>
This law mandates the prevention and redressal of sexual harassment of women at the workplace.
It requires employers to set up an Internal Complaints Committee (ICC) in organizations and an Local Complaints Committee (LCC) in districts to address complaints and grievances of sexual harassment.<br />
   <b> 4. Dowry Prohibition Act, 1961</b>
This law prohibits the giving or receiving of dowry in marriage. It aims to prevent the dowry system and reduce violence or harassment related to dowry demands.
The act allows women to file complaints against individuals demanding dowry, with penalties for both the giving and receiving parties.\n\n
    <b>5. The Immoral Traffic (Prevention) Act, 1956 (ITPA)</b>
This act seeks to prevent human trafficking and exploitation, particularly the trafficking of women and children for commercial sexual exploitation.
It provides strict punishment for trafficking and aims to rescue and rehabilitate victims.\n\n
   <b> 6. The Protection of Children from Sexual Offences Act, 2012 (POCSO)</b>
While it covers children, the law is often used in cases involving minor girls and offers comprehensive protection against sexual abuse, assault, harassment, and pornography involving minors.
It sets strict punishments and ensures special courts handle these cases to provide timely justice.\n\n
   <b> 7. The Maternity Benefit Act, 1961 (Amended in 2017)</b>
This act entitles women employees to maternity benefits, such as paid leave for up to 26 weeks, along with provisions for nursing breaks and crèche facilities at the workplace.\n\n
    <b>8. Indecent Representation of Women (Prohibition) Act, 1986</b>
This law prohibits indecent representation of women through advertisements, publications, writings, paintings, or any other means.
It aims to curb the objectification of women in media and advertisements.\n\n
    <b>9. The Medical Termination of Pregnancy (MTP) Act, 1971 (Amended in 2021)</b>
The MTP Act allows women to legally terminate pregnancies under specific conditions, offering access to safe and legal abortion.
The 2021 amendment extended the gestational limit for abortion to 24 weeks in specific cases and aims to provide greater reproductive rights to women.\n\n
    <b>10. The Criminal Law (Amendment) Act, 2013 (Nirbhaya Act)</b>
After the 2012 Delhi gang rape case, this amendment strengthened existing laws to address sexual violence.
It redefined rape, introduced new offenses (such as stalking and acid attacks), and increased the punishments for these crimes.<br/>
    <b>These laws are part of India’s ongoing efforts to provide security, dignity, and equality for women.</b></string>
</resources>
